GITA SHAVINA ISMAWATI



PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Has 3 years experience in the Procurement division by handling requirements (especially mechanical, electrical and instrument items) from several Oil and Gas Companies in Indonesia such as BP Berau LTD, PT Pertamina Hulu Energi, PT Medco E&P Indonesia and many others

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

SMAN 20 JAKARTA

2014 - 2017 MIPA

CONTACT

Address : Jl. Bendungan Jago RTO13

RWO01 No.7 Kemayoran,

Jakarta Pusat

Email: gitashavina96@gmail.com

Phone : 085719855022

LinkedIn : www.linkedin.com/in/gita-shavina

HARD SKILL

Microsoft Word - Very Experienced
Microsoft Excel - Very Experienced
Microsoft Outlook - Very Experienced
Microsoft Powerpoint - Very Experienced

SOFT SKILL

Leadership - Experienced
Team Work - Very Experienced
Negotiation - Experienced
Administration and Inventory Management
- Very Experienced
Sourcing Skills and Product Knowledge

- Very Experienced

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accounting and Administration PT MAGNA GLOBAL TRANS

2017 - 2018

- Managing office financial books and office financial reports.
- Check and verify the completeness and validation of documents related to financial transactions.
- Managing all documents for the process of releasing goods from the port.
- Arrange the delivery of goods from the country of origin to the recipient's warehouse

Procurement

PT TAIRAN HAHAI MANDIRI

2018 - 2021

- Managed all processes related to the tender requirements.
- · Clarifying and negotiating with clients if required.
- Managing inventories and maintaining accurate purchase, pricing records, delivery time, etc.
- Maintaining delivery of goods to the final destination as required by client as stated on the Purchase order.
- Maintaining good supplier and vendor relations and agreement.

Admin Purchasing

CV. WAHANA MITRAKARYA NUSANTARA

2021 - 2022

- Managed administration doc related to the bid requirements.
- · Control project income and expenses
- Managing office administration and project administration
- Suppliers and vendors sourcing for projects
- Release PO for vendors
- Received purchase request and make payments.

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia - Expert English - Good